<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="plants">
        <item>Aloe Vera</item>
        <item>English Ivy</item>
        <item>Spider Plant</item>
        <item>Snake Plant</item>
        <item>Calathea</item>
        <item>Palm Tree</item>
        <item>Chinese money plant</item>
        <item>Ficus</item>
        <item>Calamondin Orange Tree</item>
        <item>Jade Plant</item>
        <item>Alocasia Zebrina</item>
        <item>Guzmania</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="lightRequirements">
        <item>Indirect or direct sunlight.</item>
        <item>flourishes in bright, indirect light. But can grow anywhere.</item>
        <item>Spider plants prefer bright light for maximum growth but will still flourish in indirect and fairly low amounts of light.</item>
        <item>Indirect or bright sunlight. </item>
        <item>Bright, indirect light. </item>
        <item>Bright indirect light to bright shade.</item>
        <item>Bright, indirect sunlight. Rotate to obtain symmetry.</item>
        <item>Indirect sunlight</item>
        <item>direct sunlight. More sun the better</item>
        <item>Direct Sunlight</item>
        <item>Bright-light spot with indirect sunlight.</item>
        <item>Bright, natural light. Avoid exposure to any direct, hot sun</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="waterRequirements">
        <item>Allow soil to dry between watering</item>
        <item>Allow soil to dry between watering</item>
        <item>Regularly, but not so much water so that the soil it soggy (the roots can rot this way).</item>
        <item>Water rarely and make sure the dirt has fully dried between waterings</item>
        <item>Keep the soil moist but not soggy. Use distilled, spring, or rain water when possible.</item>
        <item>Water really well in the growing season little over winter. never allow the pot to stand in water.</item>
        <item>Once a week.</item>
        <item>water when the plants soil is dry a few inches down.</item>
        <item>Water thoroughly, allowing the surface of the soil to dry between waterings.</item>
        <item>Allow soil to dry between waterings.</item>
        <item>Water about twice per week in the spring and reduce to about once per week in the winter</item>
        <item>Water when the potting soil is dry to the touch and in the cup of the plant.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="funFacts">
        <item>One of aloe’s most famous uses is to soothe sunburnt skin, and it can be also used for cold sores.</item>
        <item>There are 12-15 species of ivy.</item>
        <item>Spider plants also go by the names “airplane plant,” “ribbon plant,” and “spider ivy.”</item>
        <item>Snake plants are effective at cleaning the air, removing toxins such as formaldehyde.</item>
        <item>On some varieties of Calathea it looks like there are eyes on the leaves, just like peacock feathers. That is why Calathea is also referred to as the Peacock Plant.</item>
        <item>Over 2500 species of palm trees exist today.</item>
        <item>Place a coin in the soil with your Chinese money plant, and it’ll spontaneously start to attract wealth.</item>
        <item>The name of the plant originated from Latin “Ficus” that stands for “fig.”</item>
        <item>Calamondin oranges are a dwarf citrus variety.</item>
        <item>Tortoises like to eat leaves of the jade plant. </item>
        <item>The plant is also known as Elephant\'s Ear. </item>
        <item>Guzmania dies after it has produced its flowers in summer but new plants can easily be propagated from the offsets which appear as the parent plant dies.</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="plantimages">
        <item>@drawable/image_alow_vera</item>
        <item>@drawable/image_englishivy</item>
        <item>@drawable/image_spider_plant</item>
        <item>@drawable/image_snake_plant</item>
        <item>@drawable/image_calathea</item>
        <item>@drawable/image_palm</item>
        <item>@drawable/image_pilea</item>
        <item>@drawable/image_ficus</item>
        <item>@drawable/image_calamondin</item>
        <item>@drawable/image_jade</item>
        <item>@drawable/image_zebrina</item>
        <item>@drawable/image_guzmania</item>
    </array>

    <integer-array name="favourites">
        <item>5</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>7</item>
    </integer-array>

</resources>